Lilly Library collection of press kits and other film media releases, 1975-1995 PN1997 .A1
Lilly Library
Lilly Library collection of press kits and other film media releases
1975-1995
Lilly Library
PN1997 .A1
21 Boxes
The collection includes press kits from movie productions between the years 1975 and 1995.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Biographical Note
A press kit is a pre-packaged set of promotional materials that provide information about a person, company, organization or cause and which is distributed to members of the media for promotional use. Press kits, or media kits as they are sometimes known, are often distributed to announce a release or for a news conference.
Arrangement
The collection inventory is arranged alphabetically by film title. Box 21 added at a later date, with titles out of sequence.
Scope and Content Note
The collection includes press kits from movie productions between the years 1975 and 1995. Most of the press kits are issued in individual illustrated folders and some include photographs or slides.
Advertising --Motion pictures.; Motion picture actors and actresses --United States --20th century.; Motion picture industry --United States --20th century.; Motion picture industry --Public relations.; Motion picture journalism --United States --20th century.; Motion pictures --United States --20th century.
- Press kits and other film media releases, 1975-1995
  - About Last Night (Box 1)
  - The Abyss (Box 1)
  - Action Jackson (Box 1)
  - Addams Family Values (Box 1)
  - Adventures in Babysitting (Box 1)
  - The Adventures of Buckaroo Banzai (Box 1)
  - The Adventures of Ford Fairlane (Box 1)
  - The Adventures of the Great Mouse Detective (Box 1)
  - The Adventures of Milo and Otis (Box 1)
  - The African Queen (Box 1)
  - The Age of Innocence (Box 1)
  - Agnes of God (Box 1)
  - Air America (Box 1)
  - The Air Up There (Box 1)
  - Airheads (Box 1)
  - Airplane (Box 1)
  - Alamo Bay (Box 1)
  - Alice (Box 1)
  - Alien Nation (Box 1)
  - Aliens (Box 1)
  - Aliens 3 (Box 1)
  - Alive (Box 1)
  - All I Want for Christmas (Box 1)
  - Almost an Angel, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Always, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Amadeus, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - American Anthem (Box 1)
  - American Cyborg: Steel Warrior, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - American Dreamer, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - American Flyers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - American Me, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - American Tail: Fieval Goes West, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Andre, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Angel Heart, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Angels in the Outfield, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Angie, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Another 48 Hours, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Another Stakeout, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Another You, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - April Fool's Day, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Arachnophobia, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - The Aristocats, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Armed and Dangerous, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Army of Darkness (Box 1)
  - Article 99, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Aspen Extreme (Box 1)
  - Assassination, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - At Close Range, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - At Play in the Fields of the Lord, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Avalon, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Avenging Angel (Box 1)
  - Avenging Force, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Awakenings, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - The Babe, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Baby, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 1)
  - Baby Boom (Box 1)
  - Baby's Day Out (Box 1)
  - Back to School, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Back to the Beach, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Back to the Future (Box 2)
  - Back to the Future Part II, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Back to the Future Part III, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Backdraft, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Bad Dreams (Box 2)
  - Bad Girls (Box 2)
  - Bad Influence, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Band of the Hand, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Barton Fink, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Basic Instinct (Box 2)
  - Bat 21, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Batteries Not Included, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Beaches, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - The Bear (dir. Annaud, Jean-Jacques), Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - The Bear (dir. Sarafian, Richard), Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Beauty and the Beast, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Bebe's Kids (Box 2)
  - The Bedroom Window, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Beethoven, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Beethoven's 2nd, Includes photographs or glossy prints (photographs damaged) (Box 2)
  - Before Sunrise, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - The Believers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Benji the Hunted, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Benny and Joon (Box 2)
  - Best Defense, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Best of the Best 2, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Best Seller, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Betsy's Wedding, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Beverly Hills Cop, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Beverly Hills Cop III (Box 2)
  - Big (Box 2)
  - The Big Blue, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Big Business, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - The Big Chill, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - The Big Easy, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - The Big Sleep (Box 2)
  - The Big Town, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Big Trouble in Little China (Box 2)
  - Bill and Ted's Bogus Journey, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Billy Bathgate, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Billy Madison (Box 2)
  - Biloxi Blues, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Bird on a Wire, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Black Cauldron, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Black Rain (Box 2)
  - Black Widow, Includes slides (Box 2)
  - Blank Check, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Blankman (Box 2)
  - Blaze, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Blind Date, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - The Blob, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Blue Chips, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Blue City, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Blue Steel (Box 2)
  - Blue Thunder, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Blue Velvet, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 2)
  - Body Double, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Body Parts, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Body Rocks, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Boomerang (Box 3)
  - Born American, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Born in East L.A., Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Born on the Fourth of July, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Born Yesterday, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Boyz N the Hood, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Brain Donors (Box 3)
  - Breakin' 2: Electric Boogaloo, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Brewster's Millions (Box 3)
  - The Bride, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Bright Lights, Big City, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Broadcast News (Box 3)
  - A Bronx Tale, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Bugs Bunny: His Fabulous Fiftieth (Box 3)
  - Bugsy, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Bull Durham, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - The 'burbs, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Bushwhacked (Box 3)
  - The Butcher's Wife, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Bye Bye, Love (Box 3)
  - CB4 (Box 3)
  - Cabin Boy, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Cadillac Man, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Calendar Girl (Box 3)
  - Camp Nowhere, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Candyman (Box 3)
  - Can't Buy Me Love, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Cape Fear, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Captain Ron (Box 3)
  - Care Bears Movie II: A New Generation, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Career Opportunities, Includes photographs or glossy prints (photographs damaged) (Box 3)
  - Carlito's Way, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Casual Sex?, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Casualties of War, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Cat's Eye (Box 3)
  - The Cemetery Club, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Chances Are, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Chaplin, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - The Chase, (1994) (Box 3)
  - Cheech & Chong's The Corsican Brothers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Cheetah, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Children of a Lesser God, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Child's Play, Includes photographs or glossy prints (original folder torn) (Box 3)
  - Child's Play 2, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Child's Play 3, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - A Chorus Line, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Christmas in Connecticut, Includes slides (Box 3)
  - Cinderella ( Theatrical Re-Release), 1987 (Box 3)
  - Circle of Friends (Box 3)
  - City of Hope (Box 3)
  - City of Joy (Box 3)
  - Class Action (Box 3)
  - Clear and Present Danger (Box 3)
  - Cliffhanger (Box 3)
  - Club Paradise (Box 3)
  - Clue, Includes photographs or glossy prints (original folder wrinkled, apparently water damaged) (Box 3)
  - Coal Miner's Daughter, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 3)
  - Cobra, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Cocktail, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Cocoon (Box 4)
  - Cocoon: The Return (Box 4)
  - The Color of Money, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Color of Night, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - The Color Purple, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Colors, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Come See the Paradise (Box 4)
  - Commando, Includes slides (Box 4)
  - The Commitments (Box 4)
  - Company Business (Box 4)
  - Compromising Positions, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Conan the Destroyer (Box 4)
  - Coneheads, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Consenting Adults (Box 4)
  - The Cook, the Thief, His Wife and Her Lover (Box 4)
  - Cool Runnings, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Cops and Robbersons (Box 4)
  - The Cotton Club (Box 4)
  - The Couch Trip, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Country, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Coupe de Ville, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - The Cowboy Way, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Crazy People, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Creepshow, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Creepshow 2, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Crimes and Misdemeanors, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides from Orion Pictures coming attractions (Box 4)
  - Crimes of Passion, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Crimes of the Heart, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Crimson Tide, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Criss Cross (Box 4)
  - Critical Condition, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Crocodile Dundee, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Crooklyn, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Crossroads (Box 4)
  - The Crow (Box 4)
  - Cry-Baby, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Cry Freedom, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - The Cure (Box 4)
  - The Cutting Edge (Box 4)
  - D2: The Mighty Ducks, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - D.A.R.Y.L. (Box 4)
  - D.O.A., Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Dakota, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Dances with Wolves, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Dangerous Game, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Dangerous Liaisons, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Dangerously Close, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Dad, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Darkman (Box 4)
  - Date with an Angel, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - Days of Thunder, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 4)
  - The Dead (Box 5)
  - Dead Again, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Dead Heat, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Dead of Winter (Box 5)
  - Dead Poets Society, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Dead Ringers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Deadly Friend, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Death Before Dishonor, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Death Warrant (Box 5)
  - Death Wish 3, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Death Wish 4, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Deceived, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Deepstar Six, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Delirious (Box 5)
  - The Delta Force (Box 5)
  - Delta Force 2 (Box 5)
  - Dennis the Menace, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Desperate Hours (Box 5)
  - Desperately Seeking Susan, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Destiny Turns on the Radio, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Dick Tracy (Box 5)
  - Die Hard, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Die Hard 2: Die Harder, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 5)
  - Diggstown (Box 5)
  - Dirty Dancing, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Dirty Rotten Scoundrels, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Disorganized Crime, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - The Distinguished Gentleman (Box 5)
  - Do the Right Thing, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - The Doctor, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Dr. Giggles (Box 5)
  - Down and Out in Beverly Hills, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Dracula (Box 5)
  - Dragnet, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Dragon, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - The Dream Team, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - The Dresser, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Driving Miss Daisy, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Drop Zone (Box 5)
  - A Dry White Season (Box 5)
  - DuckTales: The Movie - Treasure of the Lost Lamp, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Dune, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Dutch (Box 5)
  - Dying Young (Box 5)
  - Ed Wood, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Educating Rita, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Edward Scissorhands, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides; Includes pop-up book (Box 5)
  - The Efficiency Expert (Box 5)
  - Eight Men Out, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Eight Million Ways to Die, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - Eighteen Again, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 5)
  - The Elephant Man, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Elvira, Mistress of the Dark (Box 6)
  - The Emerald Forest, Includes photographs or glossy prints (original folder wrinkled, torn) (Box 6)
  - Encino Man, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Enemies: A Love Story, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 6)
  - Enemy Mine, Includes slides (Box 6)
  - Ernest Goes to Jail, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Ernest Saves Christmas, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Ernest Scared Stupid, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Eve of Destruction, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Everybody Wins, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Evil Dead II: Dead by Dawn, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Ewok Adventure, Includes slides (Box 6)
  - Exit to Eden, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - The Exorcist III (Box 6)
  - Explorers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Extreme Prejudice, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Extremities, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - F/X, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - FX2 Deadly Art of Illusion, Includes photographs or glossy prints (photographs damaged) (Box 6)
  - The Fabulous Baker Boys, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 6)
  - Falcon and the Snowman, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Falling From Grace (Box 6)
  - Falling in Love, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - The Family (Box 6)
  - Family Business, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Fanny and Alexander (Theatrical Re-Release), Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Fantasia (Theatrical Re-Release), Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Far and Away, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Far from Home (Box 6)
  - A Far Off Place, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Farewell to the King, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 6)
  - Fast Forward, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Fat Man and Little Boy, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Fatal Beauty (Box 6)
  - Fatal Instinct (Box 6)
  - Father Hood, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Father of the Bride, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Fern Gully ... The Last Rainforest (Box 6)
  - Ferris Bueller's Day Off, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - A Few Good Men, Includes slides (Box 6)
  - Field of Dreams, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Fifty-two Pick-Up (Box 6)
  - A Fine Mess, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Fire Birds, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Fire in the Sky (Box 6)
  - Fire with Fire, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - The Firm, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - The First Power, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Firstborn, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - A Fish Called Wanda (Box 6)
  - The Fisher King, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - The Five Heartbeats (Box 6)
  - The Flamingo Kid, Includes slides (Box 6)
  - Flashback, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Flatliners, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 6)
  - Flesh + Blood, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Flesh and Bone, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Fletch Lives, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Flight of the Innocent (Box 7)
  - Flight of the Intruder, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Flight of the Navigator, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - The Flintstones (Box 7)
  - Flowers in the Attic, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Fluke (Box 7)
  - The Fly, Includes slides (Box 7)
  - The Fly II (Box 7)
  - Folks! (Box 7)
  - Follow That Bird, Includes photographs or glossy prints (folder torn, water damaged) (Box 7)
  - For Keeps (Box 7)
  - For Love or Money, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - For the Boys, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 7)
  - Forrest Gump (Box 7)
  - The Fourth War (Box 7)
  - 1492: Conquest of Paradise (Box 7)
  - The Fox and the Hound (Theatrical Re-Release), Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Freddie as F.R.O.7. (Box 7)
  - French Kiss (Box 7)
  - Fresh (Box 7)
  - Fresh Horses, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - The Freshman, (1990); Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Friday the 13th Part VI: Jason Lives, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Friday the 13th Part VIII: Jason Takes Manhattan, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Friday the 13th A New Beginning, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Fried Green Tomatoes, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Fright Night, Includes photographs or glossy prints (folder water damaged) (Box 7)
  - From the Hip, Includes photographs or glossy prints (folder torn) (Box 7)
  - Funny About Love, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Funny Bones, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Gandhi (Box 7)
  - Garbo Talks, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Gardens of Stone, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Gate II, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Geronimo: An American Legend (Box 7)
  - The Getaway (Box 7)
  - Ghost, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Ghost Dad, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Ghost Busters II, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Girls Just Want to Have Fun, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Gladiator (Box 7)
  - The Glass Menagerie, (1987); Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Glory, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 7)
  - The Godfather Part III, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - The Golden Child, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Gone With the Wind - 50th Anniversary, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Good Morning Vietnam, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - The Good Mother, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - The Good Son (Box 7)
  - Goodfellas, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - A Goofy Movie, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Gorillas in the Mist, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Gotcha! (Box 7)
  - Grand Canyon (Box 7)
  - Graveyard Shift, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Great Balls of Fire, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - The Great Mouse Detective, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - The Great Outdoors, Includes photographs or glossy prints (folder damaged) (Box 7)
  - Green Card, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - The Grifters, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 7)
  - Groundhog Day (Box 8)
  - The Guardian, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Guarding Tess (Box 8)
  - Guilty as Sin, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - The Gun in Betty Lou's Handbag (Box 8)
  - Gung Ho, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Gymkata (Box 8)